Did you not hear what Allah
commanded
the messenger to say,
Salatu was-salam, that
My Salat, my devotion in
Salah,
all everything I do in my
life
regarding
reverence for Allah, and the
entirety of
my existence itself as an
individual,
Lillah, it's for Allah.
No Caesar, no division
between Caesar.
No,
Caesar does not have
anything.
In fact, in our obedience of
our
leaders,
who told us to be in our
leaders? Did Allah not say to
us
in the Quran that
that the Prophet Muhammad not
give us
proof whose guidance about
governance
and obedience to constituted
authority?
In all of that as we obey
our leaders,
well as we lead us,
there are instructions in the
Quran and
the Sunnah.
There are instructions in the
Quran and
the Sunnah about leading
itself,
about being a judge if you
are
a judge in the court of law.
What do you judge?
How do you judge?
What are rulings itself?
In fiqhul Islam, there is
kitab al-qabr,
rulings, judgments
that you must understand to
be able
to gain the ability to also
give
judgments in similar cases,